#1039: Mount Hua by sword

„Li Xiao Yao, do you sit here, are waiting mildewy?” Liu Ying as if drank somewhat many, on the face was having the meaning of despising, said: „That side has the big two, big three students to play to seize the life dart game, didn't you bring Lin Wan Er and Dong Cheng Yue to watch the fun in the past? Sits does not have the meaning here is?”

„Seizes the life dart?” My corners of the mouth raise: „Does not have the interest.”

„Is afraid of losing?” Liu Ying visits me, said: „Looks at your this, it is estimated that cannot lose.”

I let somebody cool off or calm down say with a smile: „, How does slight the law?”

„You knew in the past.”

„Hey”

I put out a hand to hold the hand of Lin Wan Er, said: „Walks, we had a look in the past, as if that side is truly lively.”

Lin Wan Er probably thinks funny, said with a smile low voice: „Pig head, were you so how easy to be prodded?”

„Was not prodded, but thought that this group of mortals need to be taught.”

„Good”

Dong Cheng Yue, Tang Qi, Tang Gu and the others also passed with us, sees only angle light of banquet hall to be brightly lit, one group of students in gathering round a giant gathering place playing amusement, but on the distant wall, plays the target of dart to be hanging on the wall, one group of students are also playing may not, not only there is a Liu Ying, even Wang Ze Cheng unexpectedly also here, but his side brings a hair to select to dye the white female student, compared with Xu Yue must attractive, really be tall Fushuai, trades the speed of girlfriend to be really quick!

„Comes, makes way.”

Liu Ying is grasping the wine class, said with a smile: „Li Xiao Yao must join ‚Mount Hua’ this to play by sword.”

„Did Mount Hua discuss the sword?” I stare.

A nearby big four school leader with a smile explained: „This game is this, each participant must lead a female companion, then Shan Tiao plays the dart, altogether three dart opportunities, start the beforehand female companion to say dart hit to make the opposite party the male throw the dart, if the enemy has hit really the similar number of times, can kiss your female companion one time, you are also same , after having won the opposite party, can win hit same motherfucker, a coin, what kind, dares to play?”

I stare, knit the brows: „Is this changes the girlfriend to play?”

The school leader smiled: „Not, kisses, does not have anything at the worst.”

Liu Ying said with a smile in side: „Doesn't dare to play? If you play, I accompany you to play one, how is it?”

Saying, falling of his vision provocation in me and on Lin Wan Er.

My brow raises, said: „Do you have the girlfriend?”

„Who said?”

Liu Ying zhang hand holds in the arms the female student who side that has worn the cream-colored tutu, said with a smile: „Mila, accompanies me to play one game, how is it?”

That is called the mila female student to eat to smile: „? Let Li Xiao Yao kiss, probably, others quite shy!”

I sneer secretly, you sufficed!

Liu Ying continued: „What kind , do you dare to play?”

I let go smile: „Oh, I must elect a girlfriend to accompany you to play two, since Schoolmate Liu Ying wants to play, that must certainly make you play to enjoy oneself to the full!”

Saying, I put out a hand to hold the arm of Tang Gu to entrain him, said: „This is my female companion, comes the human, hoodwinks his eye”

Liu Ying whole body one thump: „Your you sufficed!”

I sneer: „What's wrong, do you also shut out my female companion to come?”

The Tang Gu complexion is pale: „I especially also shuts out him to be good?”

I stared his one eyes: „You also do not have the girlfriend, selects food to do!”

„I the good and evil must select especially female!”

„”

At this time, Wang Ze Cheng carried the wine class saying: „Li Xiao Yao, you use the man to come, when shield, didn't this have the meaning? The Liu Hua University students know that the first beautiful woman Lin Wan Er boyfriend doubtful is you, do you also want to deny inadequately?”

I said: „What elects is the female companion, is not the girlfriend.”

Side, Lin Wan Er is nipping red lip, in the beautiful eye is passing spunk, obviously she does not want to play this game, after all, a proud girl will not allow the man who does not like to kiss her.

In I hesitate in making a move, suddenly a girl went out of the crowd, said: „Since this, do not press Xiao Yao, I come, when Xiao Yao female companion? What kind, dares to play?”

I looked at the past, this girl was not others, was Liu Tiantian, girl who was good to uphold justice, if I did not have girlfriend definitely you!

„Wan Er, Ok?” I asked.

Lin Wan Er nods: „Um, do not lose! Lost one time to take a coin!”

„A coin, is anything”

That „they said that is 10,000 motherfucker”

„Scratches, this must win!”

Liu Ying is holding the hand of new girlfriend, but Liu Tiantian also made use to pull my arm to arrive at the middle, the dart distance target about 5 meters high and low, actually the hit probability was very high.

„Started?” Liu Ying asked.

I said: „5 meters, were too near, was too easy?”

„How many do you think?”

„Three times, 15 meters how is it?”

„This”

„Doesn't dare to play?”

„Has anything not to dare, plays plays!”

Therefore the backlash, in our manpower three darts, from the target about 15 meters, the ordinary people definitely could not hit the target, but Liu Ying is in the master, can not know.

Liu Tiantian stands side me, said with a smile: „Dear, I said how many are quite good?”

„3, visit him to have this skill.”

„Good!”

Therefore under the rightness of school leader, Liu Tiantian said 3, Liu Ying must three rounds in three be able to win.

The Mila also corners of the mouth raised, said 3, this was the going all out rhythm.

Liu Ying comes first, the body sinks slightly, the judgment distance and effort, lifted the hand dart to exit suddenly, „” sewed in the lower extremity of target, almost must miss the target, was very dangerous.

He has licked the lip , to continue second, „”, this time has adjusted the effort, on some, has hit, is really the master!

Third, this time Liu Ying continues the air/Qi to decide emanation with rapt attention, but this luck is not good, the dart has not contacted the target from the start.

He lost, is one's turn me.

Deeply inspires, in the palms is passing the light Yang Yan bracing cold, but this group of people are not the followers, should unable to see my essence Yang Yanjin, Tang Qi could.

Almost does not have any gap, I every. seconds a projection, „” consecutively three, three darts sewed in the red star place, one group of students were immediately dumbfounded, quick, the surrounding female student was screaming cheered, even many female students started to flirt with the eyes, this was not a very good custom, liked a person not being able because of his some merit, for example these female students perhaps think that I threw the dart to like me well, but actually does not know that I did like taking a bath and digging out the foot guy and others.

„Has won, we won!”

Liu Tiantian cheers, opened the hand to grasp me, the white stomacher almost fell, I hurried well-mannered pushed her to leave, says with a smile: „Um, 3 coins, our half minute?”

„Um good!”

Liu Ying face dying embers, said: „Was too far!”

That mila with a smile said: „Xiao Yao Zi Zai, you, if must kiss me a bit faster to come, missed this village not to have this shop, again when wants to have this opportunity not to know!”

I show a faint smile, said: „I took three coins to be good, gave up as for the chip of kiss, I have not kissed the custom of others girlfriend, Mr. Liu Ying, three coins thank you, took the money quickly!”

Generally speaking the rich man will not bring that many cashes, is good has the ATM ATM because of side, Liu Ying immediately dingily has taken the money, but Liu Tiantian as if really very likes me, Lin Wan Er and Dong Cheng Yue, god knows her will do to have an accident, such female student is too not really self-possessed, one year ago my unmarried time how not to see her to appear! I in moral nature silently is thinking. Now had Lin Wan Er, other female students truly could not cancel my interest.

When you fall in love with a woman wholeheartedly, in this world was only two women, was she, as well as was not she.

When at the meeting of Liu Hua University plays about 10 points diverges, after nearly two hours of trying to get close, I and Lin Wan Er, Dong Cheng Yue also repeatedly helps, finally that stature hot Dong Ling no longer has repelled to Tang Gu, because I told her, although Tang Gu this person of undistinguished appearance, but the moral nature deep place has the universe, belongs to that righteousness Bo Yuntian, the muck Wang Hou real man, these two words as if touch a stretch of soft domain that Dong Ling heart of hearts has needed to protect, finally started to give up with the eyeglasses brother speaks.

Eyeglasses brother whole face sunset glow picked up the little girl, but I and went out, take taxi to go to making of Shen Bing with Lin Wan Er, Dong Cheng Yue and Tang Qi, today's second, goes to the PaPa bar to support, and familiar one there environment was also good, when protecting Lin Wan Er, I should also consider the completeness of Shen Bing, although in the bar many people were the people in base, but was not quite as before safe, for money and benefit, some people became is not the human, can do any cruel matter.

Arrives in the bar time, the unexpected business is especially good, has almost soon been fully occupied, Shen Bing has not come out to meet with me directly, approximately as a result of the relations of status, but sends out a server to bring us, after arranges the nice wine water to us, she appeared finally, a black evening dress, the makings of night shop queen are full.

Actually has drunk many liquor, but Shen Bing drew us to drink many liquor as before, afterward she greeted other frequent guests to go, left behind me and Lin Wan Er, Dong Cheng Yue plays the game of small honeybee together, after around 12 : 00 o'clock at night, finally was exhausted, but truly also very relaxed, the King in game will hunt for among struggling with NPC to make me too tired, had the opportunity of this relaxation rarely.

Returning on the way, Lin Wan Er by has fallen asleep in my arms unexpectedly, the beautiful cheek is bringing bright red.

„Drop!”

On the cell phone, a news came from Yue Qing Qian: „Brother Xiao Yao, cold uncultivated land Dragon’s den receives the Hybrid Demon small scale attack, I and Li Mu had the human to brush the duty, you and can Sister Cang Tong come?”

I reply: „Has king level BOSS to appear?”

„No.”

„You play happily, I drank, sleep.”

„Good!”

#1073: Horrible price

„Hey!”

In the eye of ancient musical scale gushes out to kill intent, urging the horse to clash, the long sword in the hand, was actually ready, most fearful was this match, the pointed weapons gathers the potential in the bosom, can actually launch the attack from any angle, this was a blossomless skillful murder art, perhaps the ancient musical scale was not one practices the person of sword in the reality, but in the game, absolutely is the master of this murder art.

I stand in the cold wind gorgeously, the war is just luxurious, the strong winds also wreak havoc, blows the Zixiao cape dance behind, the white cape was been incarnadine by the blood, above also keeps the hole hole that arrows and lances are puncturing thoroughly, appears very distressed, my which also a little that day plume empire of present greatly holds the spear and [Zhan Long] Guildmaster impressive and dignified manner.

Town Yue Dao delivers rapidly, my direct impact in the past, asked the way by town Yue Daolai!

In the eye of ancient musical scale passed over gently and swiftly a startled color, understands instantaneously I am also in the master, selects in the [Assault] sword blade edge unexpectedly on the way, swings the town Yue Dao at the same time left fist to gather the potential to send, blood red fist seal falls on my front together!

„67122!”

Very strong striking power, thunderstorm fist, Holy Ghost second-order skill!

In my chest obstructs, I also rapidly respond, on the butterfly sword surge golden six glow stars, the [Combo] skill in deliver instantaneously after his the ancient musical scale passed over gently and swiftly carry on the back!

„31221!”

„33818!”

„32171!”

But has only hit successfully 3 times, other three struck actually to be returned to a sword to swing by the ancient musical scale + diagonal to walk the position operation to fall to MISS, although was not Pulse Break Style, but had the Pulse Break Style skillful style very much.

„Drop!”

Yue Qing Qian has sent an information to me: „Brother Xiao Yao, I [Stealth] in my right front, coordinating me to come a sneak attack, the quickest speed massacres the ancient musical scale!”

„Good!”

The sword blade edge raises, I already opened the art of dancing of energy ghosts and gods, the surrounding hostile player will be injured continually, the ancient musical scale naturally is not willing to continue to pester with me, progresses to walk, but I raise the long sword am [Seven Star Fragment Slash], the bang cut on his road which must be taken, forcing him to obey to tend to the Yue Qing Qian stealth position.

„Day!”

The ancient musical scale has not thought that I hand over the skill to hand over that decisively, the warhorse one slanting is really thinking the right front overran , there, the Yue Qing Qian beautiful form is ambushing in the empty shade, but I lock that position to start [Assault] to move directly, must reenforce the past, otherwise she definitely is not the match of ancient musical scale, the operation and tactical awareness of ancient musical scale did not say above Yue Qing Qian that equipment was also better than her a level!

„Hey!”

Suddenly, the ancient musical scale lowered to roar, the long sword is dividing a sword to the air, simultaneously the under foot air/Qi glow surged, was starting a combo level energy to the front rapidly!

Ended!

My moral nature one cold, he knows that Yue Qing Qian does lead the way there?

The next quarter, I understood, but sentences in advance, however confirmed truly the Yue Qing Qian position actually depends upon the combo air/Qi glow, is mad the glow in surging on the way of received impediment of Yue Qing Qian body to have the subtle change, this is the judgment basis of ancient musical scale, good intelligent person!

The instance that combo erupts, the Yue Qing Qian blood strip brushes to fall, however she has also spelled, the chest by the instance that the sword blade edge punctures thoroughly, wrinkles the delicate eyebrows to wield the dagger, positive [Gouge] strikes!

The dizziness is successful!

As long as the top player, has invincible skill inevitably, Yue Qing Qian was almost killed by the instantaneous second, only with enough time wields [Gouge] to strike, but this [Gouge] strikes can actually continue 2 seconds of dizziness, at this time, I rapidly plundered , the whole body erupted together the golden ray, the distant place, the light dance melody, met with two people also to shout that without enough time, has actually ridden the wind to cut 15 swords to erupt instantaneously, directly to the back iron skull city the ancient musical scale!

And, I have to ban the grasping of special effect god, in 60 minutes ancient musical scale including resurrecting not possibly!

But looks that the body of Yue Qing Qian falls down slowly, actually as before grievedly, to kill an ancient musical scale, made our [Zhan Long] hang vice- Guildmaster.

I am unable to open the body of extinguishing not to kill the ancient musical scale, because the opposite party also has the invincibility, strikes to kill the opportunity of this top player to be fleeting, but Yue Qing Qian with is such an opportunity that the life trades, does not give the opposite party to open the invincible opportunity to kill directly!

Two tings simultaneously from the sky are reverberating

„Bites!”

System announcement: Players 【Ancient musical scale】( US) struck to kill the player successfully 【Yue Qing Qian】( China), and captures its 10% country to fight points successfully!

„Bites!”

System announcement: Players 【Xiao Yao Zi Zai】( China) struck to kill the player successfully 【Ancient musical scale】( US), and captures its 10% country to fight points successfully!

Not far away, the fierce combat is continuing as before, Wang Jian already the remnant blood, raised is breaking the sea sword to retrocede rapidly, on the face full is the spunk, but in his rear area, the sky rose came finally!

„East city, does skill of Aiersha scepter have CD?” I look up to the city.

Dong Cheng Yue is resigned-looking: „Before 4 hours, has used one time, must wait again for 8 hours”

I have fired into the sky rose rapidly, cannot wait, waited for Wang Jian and Li Mu will again die in battle once more, although my strengths to these two brothers was very confident, but the strength disparate pendulum there, equipment, skill and the Level all-round strength sky rose absolutely was the world first three ranks, perhaps, was first.

„Wang Jian, to here!” My loud [say / way].

Wang Jian is light smiles: „Does not use, the Xiao Yao elder brother, I gives you and Li Mu Boss creates the opportunity!”

Saying, him was drawing the reins to retrocede suddenly, presents stance that backed up to march forward, simultaneously raised the breaking sea sword in hand, started skill instantaneously, making us unable to think that broke the sea sword to emerge waves, divided suddenly, carried over the dreadful rough sea waves to wreak havoc in the crowd, but the sky rose bore the brunt, naturally did not evade.

However, why peak master is the peak master , because can make the matter that the ordinary player cannot think, when breaks the sea to strike to divide, the sky rose beautiful corners of the mouth rise slightly, mobilized Jianfeng to advance the skill directly, the body changes into a lightning to clash from the mighty waves, the goal locked Wang Jian directly, the blade edge of bang that lava the superelevation erupted in the Wang Jian front.

„112928!”

Wang Jian definitely is invincible skill in CD, or after mediating sea fury points was insufficient, was massacred directly!

„Bites!”

System announcement: Players 【Sky rose】( US) struck to kill the player successfully 【General Wang Jian】( China), and captures its 10% country to fight points successfully!

[Seven Stars Teleportation] from the sky glitters, I rushed to the sky rose front rapidly, [Binding Chains] have closed off her backlash path, town Yue Dao sweep away, „bang” surged together Mars on her chest Armor, carried over 51023 points injury digit, simultaneously sword blade edge maneuver [Tempest Sword] + trod the broken heavenly thunder to start together, was almost exhausts all skills to attack.

The sky rose was broken the sea to stroke, turned into the remnant blood instantaneously, but the look on face is as before tranquil, after the sword blade edge standard keeps off under me strikes, makes use the backlash, the next effect that Jianfeng advances locks Li Mu outrageously.

„Li Mu, invincible!” I shout hurriedly.

The Li Mu reaction rate has missed one, the dragon bone sword ray twinkle of sky rose, transforms a big dragon winding around Li Mu, unexpectedly can ban launch of skill, and makes Li Mu unable to move, the dragon bone sword wielded continuously several times, Li Mu HP already saw the bottom, the speed that but I chased down was also fast, the sky rose could not massacre Li Mu shortly, retreated decisively.

But, Li Mu absolutely is the unyielding man, less than 10% HP, outrageously start the [Assault] skill, „brushing” one pursues the sky rose, instantaneous that the match for ten thousand skill opens hits in the waist of sky rose!

„Bang!”

The anger does not touch Zhoushan!

Sky rose miserable snort, this time hit enough painful, after drinking up health potion, HP that restored also was less than 15%, but Li Mu were less, was only fired by opposite party mount remaining is less than 6% HP.

„Really repugnant!”

The sky rose knitting the brows instantaneous sword light passed over gently and swiftly, immediately Li Mu also knelt.

„Bites!”

System announcement: Players 【Sky rose】( US) struck to kill the player successfully 【General Li Mu】( China), and captures its 10% country to fight points successfully!

Li Mu this time chases down has not actually wasted, he strove for at least 2 seconds of Cooldown, this has sufficed, because I saw a familiar form in the crowd, Meng Yao raised the Lady Wa stone to have a bloody road in the crowd of US war zone, from reversed direction direct impact sky rose, started the SSS level instantaneously the ruling skill!

„Bang!”

Hits to faint successfully, dizziness 3 seconds!

But player in one crowd of US war zones adds the blood to the sky rose, the Meng Yao striking power is not considered as top, wants to kill her not to be easy.

However, 3 seconds were enough regarding me!

A on the way of [Great Realm of Desolation] locking sky rose of terminal velocity flight, reduces her 50% by the treatment result, the butterfly was being surged the radiant sword glow, rides the wind CD that cuts just well to cool, kills!

The golden rays of 19 levels of god level skills shoot up to the sky, the instantaneous 15 sword air/Qi puncture thoroughly the body of sky rose!

The second kills!

„Bites!”

System announcement: Players 【Xiao Yao Zi Zai】( China) struck to kill the player successfully 【Sky rose】( US), and captures its 10% country to fight points successfully!

What a pity, I am not Old K, does not have that high knock rating, only blew out the wrister of sky rose, the three stars magical instrument, throws the guild warehouse directly, came to compensate as the level to Wang Jian or Li Mu.

„Bang bang bang” the sound is unceasing, the sky rose dies, the armies in entire iron skull city almost fell into a group of people without a leader region, but in my behind southern city wall, the melt god cavalry leaps the city wall in abundance, the summon warhorse, prepared [Assault].

Looks at chilly beautiful picture under city, my cannot help but moral nature shivers, Yue Qing Qian, Li Mu, Wang Jian, Star Blade and the others died in battle, but chases down to meet with, light dance melody and other ABN to fight the price of net master, was One Second Hero, Death God’s Elegy, Old K, Wolf, Fox and the others the bodies completely lies down in the ruins.

„Was too miserable”

General Bai Qi raises fully is being Axe of blood, arrives at side me, said: „Guildmaster, the brothers hung quickly”

I nod silently, said: „Brothers have achieved, we delay them in the Fan Shu City five days five nights, we facing have not drawn back compared with we stronger match timidly, [Zhan Long] does right by Tian Ling Empire, the Chinese war zone should be proud of my brothers!”

In the general Bai Qi eye is glittering some rays: „Um!”

#1086: Strength of Yang Yan the

Cooldown every little bit is passing, was set to carry out Cooldown from the duty to be also getting more and more near.

But I determined that they will certainly begin, this flock of crazed bastards as if never know that anything is called timidly . Moreover, so long as this time they dare to begin, showed once more bred to install the science and technology is not together the domestic crime, but was one related to the international and deliberate turmoil manufacture, the situation was similar to such that Shen Bing said is truly getting more and more serious.

I gain ground to have a look at the sky, is JC, can do protects the safety of people with the life, but now we do also this.

„B group attention alert.”

In the miniature earphone transmits order in the control center, here is just facing the street, once were attacked, is probably easiest to withstand the firepower the place.

Quick, 4 : 17 arrived, but did not have what sound in all directions as before.

„What's the matter?” Xing Lie somewhat could not endure.

I said in a soft voice: „Calm , to continue.”

This was also the crowd most crowded time, control center there did not have what news, but informed us to strengthen the alert.

Several minutes later, in 4 : 25, the distant place walked one crowd to select the shoulder pole, to take the person who the snake leather bag was wrapping, seems like work who came from the rural area, had the male to have the female, but I induced rapidly, this group of people had the vicious tendencies, that type of vicious tendencies could not conceal, to aura practiced at my many years, can catch very much easily.

„Was careful that group of people, they are the camouflages.” I said in a low voice.

Xing Lie has turned around, shows a faint smile: „Looks like is only fellow villager of one crowd of working, all right”

His voice just fell, not far away that carried the shoulder pole and a face overly cautious and prudent person actually to trade an expression, on the face completely was the color of hatred sea, cried to discard the shoulder pole, pulled out at least 40 centimeters fruit knife from the basket, hugged child's mother to chop to the one side, the mouth scolded the words that some I could not be understanding.

Hesitates?

Almost I have made the decision instantaneously, lifted the hand to draw out opening fire of waist pistol quickest speed!

„Bang!”

The sound of gunfire resounds, the nano bullet penetrated his forehead, explodes directly in the cerebellum, blood plasma with ** spatters in all directions together.

„?” Xing Lie astonished.

Not far away, about 20 + people almost draw out the blade together, fires into the innocent crowd that escaped and called out in alarm in all directions, the axe is grasping the stock, said: „This group of people do not breed to think of the human, is only the average person, what to do?”

Beyond five meters, a wear „simple” the middle-aged woman of clothes raises the blade, pursues one about 7, 8-year-old little girls, the little girl is frightening hum to cry, runs while cries, I no longer wait for anything, before an arrow step rushes, the fist delivers!

„!”

A sad fist, is almost broken to the bang the cervical vertebra of this middle-aged woman, her body after revolves several layer on layer falls to the ground, is killed violently at the scene!

Is the team leader of Hangzhou squad, I commanded in a low voice: „Does not use hesitant, wants what to pity to the person who child starts? Begins to me, the above order has not requested to grasp lives, executes completely at the scene, this person does not need [Judgement]!”

Xing Lie also no longer said anything, draws out the pistol aiming, (spear|gun) taking down.

Axe and the others are also the skilled people of murder, eliminates here 20 + people rapidly, but we do not have casualties, even common people also under our lightning attacks does not have a point to injure.

The square ground is stained with blood, but is their. Xing Lie is grasping the pistol of belching smoke, frowns saying: „That little girl was almost killed a moment ago”

I nod, the little girl is shrinking under the square center huge radiant gasification decoration is sobbing, I walk to go forward, received the guns, touches her head, said: „Child, do not cry, your mother?”

„Mother bought the cold drink” she to cry saying that gained ground to have a look at me, obviously has scared, asked: „Uncle, are you you are policeman?”

My gentle smiling: „Yes, I am policeman, does not need to fear that policeman will protect your.”

„Um.” Nod that she makes an effort.

In this time, suddenly in the earphone is actually transmitting ** sound: „It is not good, Southern District has danger, Li Xiao Yao, leads the member to go to Southern District reenforcement immediately! Bred to think of the human to appear!”

Mother!

I put out a hand to look that immediately a not far away GUUCI shop hides the shop employee after glass said loudly: „Helps quickly, protects this little girl.”

Sales clerk female guts but actually also big, ran to hold the hand of little girl to enter the shop, afterward closed.

My first one crooked, is hinting to the people: „, Continues to carry out the task!”

Dashes about wildly to Southern District of market, when we rush, here has just liked is a gun battle big piece is the same, several black Buick commerce stop in the roadside, rear one group of black clothed men to the front fire, but what the dead ahead is responsible for the square security is the member of Shanghai protector squad, three members fall down, bleeds seriously.

„Roar!”

Low and deep roaring, an arm of after ringer is hit, immediately entered the beast condition, the whole body grew the crowded green hair unexpectedly, the wound that bullet penetrated rapidly was also healing.

Xing Lie said in a low voice: „Very strong cicatrization ability.”

I glance side, almost does not have any good grazing point, has to clench teeth: „Goes to elevator there to seek the shield, Xing Lie goes upstairs, seeks for the best ambush point!”

„Yes!”

I behind carry the long butterfly, what Xing Lie behind carries is the sniper's rifle, in the Hangzhou squad only ambush marksmanship can with the person who I struggle high below be he.

After seeking for the grazing point, I also discovered that in the square has been lying down several corpses of common people, it seems like that this crowd bred to think of the human to go well, regardless of the result were what kind, they made the chaotic goal to achieve.

„Bang!”

A sad sound of gunfire, some point of Xing Lie in building has opened fire, immediately hid one after car(riage) breeds to think of the human but actually, the nape of the neck place has been hit, but had not actually died, but the unceasing convulsion, the whole body distortion, the nail of both hands was becoming sharp, under grabbed thoughtlessly has torn the western-style clothing and shirt, revealed fully is the chest of green scale.

The B level breeds to think of the human!

I clenched teeth, said in earphone: „Brain as before is their center organizations, Xiao Lie, aims at their head fires, defeated the brain to massacre probably!”

Xing Lie: „Um, understanding!”

Is a (spear|gun), this time suffices, a C level bred to think of the human to be exploded directly, ** flowed place, the body does not move.

Finally, bred to install the people as if unable to repress, that nape of the neck was hit roared to crawl to fire into the person of Shanghai Squad lowly, finally went against clashes forward, like fully dare-to-die corps who the fire of innumerable nano ball was only injuring does not die, made the people of Shanghai Squad change countenance.

I could not repress, lifts hand to draw out behind butterfly, immediately butterfly cold [Vanguard] makes nearby axe unable to bear to praise sigh: „, Good sword!”

However, sound that in the earphone actually transmits Shanghai Squad team leader Tang Lin: „Li Xiao Yao, does not need you to help, I can handle!”

Saying, Tang Lin flushed, in hand black glove instantaneously by bracing cold disintegration, in good family fist master, my distant looked that has judged Tang Lin is the Royal Air intermediate strength, but also is good, kills the B level to breed to think of the human, this breeds to think of the human injured reluctantly after all at present.

Tang Lin roars with breeding to install a person of wrong body, the armored hand layer on layer rumbles in the chest of opposite party, brings sound that the skeleton is rupturing, is a knee hits, takes advantage of opportunity to take down the leg is tying the arms the saber, wipes, bred to install the nape of the neck of person to have a wound, but has not punctured thoroughly the nape of the neck, the opposite party condensed the scale.

„Roar!”

Breeding of going crazy thinks of the human to be terrorist, pair of claws chaotic dance, directly after Tang Forest carried on the back to leave behind wounds, the fresh pool of blood anchored to flow, he has been injured.

„Mother!”

Tang Lin becomes angry out of shame drinks one lowly, no matter also own being damaged, is a fist bang, in breeding to install on the latter nape of the neck of person, draws out the pistol, the reverse breeds to install the body of person to force in his mouth the pistol, „Bang”, the blood spatters in all directions from the cerebellum, this B level bred to think of the human also finally is reimburses.

When does not wait for Tang Lin to pant for breath, is one roars, another B level breeds to install the human to delimit his back the sharp claws, miserable howling, Tang Lin body anteversion tumbles, actually is also the man who an iron hits, the saber wields, cuts off this to breed to install the two fingers of person, simultaneously the front was delimited to injure together.

„Go away!”

Tang Lintai foot tramples, the strength of follower cannot be underestimated, is better than breeds to think of the human to be rumbled as before flies to draw back more than ten meters.

But at this time, with a sharp roar, on a face, the nape of the neck place full was person throwing of red scale stands on the vehicle roof suddenly, almost will put in order a car(riage) to crush, his eye degenerated into scarlet, the pupil enlarges infinitely, looked like a wild animal general was roaring, the goal pointed to Tang Lin, overrunning of the hands and feet used!

The A level breeds to think of the human, whole body Armor!

„Come, bastard!”

In Tang Lin hand saber one cold, condenses the aura on the saber, is breeding to think of the human to this A level maliciously to strike!

Astounding, this A level bred to think of the human to smile unexpectedly, corners of the mouth slanting rising, looked like strangely also somewhat is somewhat fierce, lifted the hand to cover entirely the fist of thick red scale to deliver!

„Bang!”

Layer on layer strikes, naked eye obvious that saber cuns (2.5cm) change into the powder pink / white, but Tang Lin palm is a very obvious distortion, miserable snort a backlash, the arm probably broke.

Really, Royal Air intermediate is not the A level breeds to install the match of person.

„Bang!”

Xing Lie ambushes again, but nano bullet actually in this face covered breeding in scale to think of the human shaking flew, merely was the buckle half scale!

I lift the hand aiming to breed to install the eyes of person am a (spear|gun), but he raises the arm to come to square to keep off unexpectedly, intelligence quotient also.

„”

He gains ground to have a look at me, in the vision is passing the provocation unexpectedly, stretched out at least 30 centimeters tongue to lick fist scale the bloodstain on Tang Lin, said with a smile: „Your these followers, are some waste! Your attacks, are give us dragon blood soldier flexure to be itchy radically!”

Dragon blood soldier?

I almost smiled, this group of idiots think did one have these variation scales is Long Xue the soldier?

„Protects Tang Lin!”

Drinks lowly, I have raised the butterfly to overrun, promoted the extreme at I quickest speed the aura of whole person, the butterfly instantaneously by the positive flame flame package, fired a handle scarlet red long sword, Shan Zuta jumped, by me strongest struck to divide, was in airborne sneers saying: „Your this dragon blood soldier keeps off the attack of my this follower!”

In his vision passed over gently and swiftly with amazement, actually as before raises fully is the arm of scarlet red scale comes to square to keep off!

„!”

The sword light plunders, bringing the arm of miserable red blood to fall to the ground, in the meantime, a butterfly incomparably sharp sword has cut from his nape of the neck place, chops again from the waist.

Divide into two!

#1153: The winning side is late big

„Yo, many acquaintances?” Wang Ze Cheng laughs, on the face full is the experienced smiling face, this is the smiling face that in the commercial field many years whet, the average person does not have.

I think him, shows a faint smile: „Has not thought that Wang Zong also came.”

Wang Ze Cheng also visits me: „Captain Li also came, is really fortunately!”

Zheng Feier stares, somewhat could not understand the situation, looked like also thinks that I and Wang Ze Cheng were very ripe friends, but Zheng Feier was not a fool, naturally also understands me, no matter in the reality played with Wang Ze Cheng is a mortal enemy, to exempt fought, then raised the skirt to stand at the front, said with a smile: „Was good, the day sought, hurried to take a seat, prepares to eat meal, everybody in you! The masters were hungry”

The one side takes the master of microphone to smile awkwardly: „All right, I can also wait, you sit on main table everybody actually, can introduce oneself mutually?”

Although in same in university, but each other did not know as before that this is very normal matter.

Zheng Feier said: „I am Zheng Feier, didn't need to introduce? This is”

Her boyfriend stands, on face is having the gentle smiling face, said: „My name was Chu Tianxun, the poor boyfriend, vice- director of Shanghai [gold/metal] lin group, good evening everybody.”

Nearby Wang Ze Cheng stands up, on the face is having the amiable smiling face, is bowing to nearby several beautiful women, says with a smile: „Didn't I need to introduce? Wang Ze Cheng, big new student, Buesst China region CEO.”

Two female students noticed that Wang Ze Cheng such spoke, the appearance that immediately somewhat could not dominate, Wang Ze Cheng this type young promising, the appearance also good youth very much had the market after all.

Tang Qi stands up: „Tang Qi, big new student.”

I also stand up: „Didn't Li Xiao Yao, need to introduce?”

This time, I have not hidden any identity, in an instant looks to Lin Wan Er, said: „I enter the Liu Hua University reason am to protect the Wan Er security, my another status is the special combat police officer, the police officer numbers 2921607, but also invited to advise much!”

On Zheng Feier face passed over gently and swiftly to be astonished however, my special police officer status Liu Hua University many people knows actually, but is only has not stated clearly, my this announced that makes them be surprised actually.

Lin Wan Er said simply sentence „Lin Wan Er” introduced oneself, Dong Cheng Yue is also same, therefore, this host table, because the arrival of Wang Ze Cheng also brings several points of awkwardness, as a result of the enticement of delicacy delicacies, eats first!

Tang Qi also knows that the Wang Ze Cheng status is very dubious, this person may with breeding to think of the human very much to be concerned, therefore said: „Does this dine some not to be as if hygienic together?”

Actually, probably he was worrying that Dong Cheng Yue and Lin Wan Er security, Wang Ze Cheng with the chopsticks have clamped the vegetable, will others eat are infected? Wang Ze Cheng is breeds to install secret of person, thinks that in the body should also have some medicament toxin?

I „lowered sound” saying: „Has not related, sees clearly, Wang Ze Cheng has eaten the vegetable, we do not move.”

My voice presses extremely lowly, about 20 meters away is unable to hear, immediately on the face of Wang Ze Cheng a paleness, such insult is the average man is unable to endure absolutely, but Wang Ze Cheng has borne, shows a faint smile: „Do we start? Quite hungry”

„Brushes”, this bastard has clamped vegetables in several dish continuously, this clearly wants to starve to death we.

Is good is polluted because of our front vegetables, while the turntable has not rotated time has clamped some vegetables to Lin Wan Er and Dong Cheng Yue, on difference that several big elbow dragging.

Eats to 50% times, starts to cut the cake, the luxurious 12 cakes, Chu Tianxun and Zheng Feier happy cuts the cake, Xian Sha other people, Wang Ze Cheng with the Chu day homing relations quite good appearance, holds side help, but I tranquil looks at the surrounding all, Wang Ze Cheng came, needed the entire gods alert.

However somewhat is actually strange, Wang Ze Cheng links a bodyguard not to have the belt today unexpectedly, is really strange, the courage may be really big, this is must face me directly, doesn't have timid intent?

However thinks not to feel strange that carefully, Wang Ze Cheng knows that I am the special police officer team leader in Hangzhou base, without evidence time I will not begin to him, therefore his here absolute safety, but he is different, I in am bright he in darkly, Wang Ze Cheng can definitely do any matter resourcefully, so long as were not caught can continue the frank and upright life under the sunlight.

Has eaten around 9 : 00 pm, then also has the party, Zheng Feier and Chu Tianxun invited warmly, but Lin Wan Er and Dong Cheng Yue looked after my look, has rejected, was as far as possible farther from Wang Ze Cheng, I invulnerability do not represent two young ladies also invulnerability, Wan Er and East city were too for me important, cannot lose them.

Escorts two young ladies to return to the dwelling, Tang Qi also with the same place, at this moment, Dong Cheng Yue stares suddenly, traces the packet, said: „Was bad”

„What's wrong?”

„My 18 S lost has forgotten probably on the table”

„This” Tang Qi is speechless: „My this helps you take.”

At this time, the Lin Wan Er cell phone has actually made a sound, is Zheng Feier telephone: „Wan Er, the cell phone of East city forgets in the dining room, I helped to take conveniently, now is going to the road of Xiyuan bar street, can you come together? Do I deliver now to you?”

Lin Wan Er said hurriedly: „Does not use, which you told me to be good because of the bar street, we took in the past.”

„Good, bar street No. 11 here, I in entrance you.”

„Good!”

Lin Wan Er just made the telephone call, the Tang Qi cell phone has made a sound, with the connection, said: „Boss, fifth goal did BOSS leave? Good I to go back to get online immediately, wait a bit me.”

Made the telephone call, Tang Qi somewhat awkwardly said: „The Q-Sword Boss' Tenglong coverall fifth triggering duty, I must go back to get online immediately, Brother Xiao Yao, young lady's cell phone troubles you to take.”

I touch the nose: „Good, you go to room to get online practice the level, I urge to go faster return.”

„Um!”

After Lin Wan Er and Dong Cheng Yue back room, confirmed that the surrounding security I go out, and distant looked at the past, a middle-aged uncle is smoking on the campus deck chair, that was the Lin Tiannan arrangement dark sentry post, in addition the young people wore the black windproof coat to hide in the water tank feed the mosquito, in the hand was grasping the ambush step, was the person who Lin Tiannan sent, basically Lin Wan Er and Dong Cheng Yue were definitely safe in the dwelling.

Has not driven, I directly soared bar street to go, the bar street in campus majority was the student party contracts, the business was inferior that outside was so fiery, but also missed to does not go.

No. 11 entrance, Zheng Feier, Chu Tianxun, the Wang Ze Cheng three people are standing there, sees me to come, on Zheng Fei stallion shakes to begin the cell phone, said with a smile: „Here!”

I walk several steps to go forward quickly, say with a smile: „Thanks.”

„Is impolite, has not thought that is Brother Xiao Yao takes the cell phone.”

„Does not have the means that the big evening's day is too black, making a female student person be upon the jump is not quite good.”

„Hee hee, yes.”

Wang Ze Cheng actually looked at my one eyes, the corners of the mouth has raised, said: „The winning side is late big, male student dark being upon the jump of is not quite safe, adds carefully ‚Brother Xiao Yao’”

I shot a look at his one eyes, shows a faint smile, said: „Way of the world is dangerous, daybreak the association comes, be not bringing always the sunglasses, was careful that which day of sunlight will shoot in the eye unable to bear.”

„Snort, many thanks reminder!”

I turn around to walk, at the same time is pondering over the Wang Ze Cheng words, the winning side is late big, what meaning?

Goes back on the way, must by it place be the flowered work place, here is also the Liu Hua University scenery most beautiful place, the botanical garden -type scenery attracts many lover here lover's rendezvouses, but the present is in the summer, the mosquito are too many, the lovers are impossible to rush to here live to suffer hardship.

I walk in the extremely quick, colored work place almost do not have any light, only then the bright star light projects.

„Rustle”

Under the energetic high degree of concentration, not far away seems not the sound that I make, and is not the wind blows the sound of leaf likely, in the thick patch of grass glitters suddenly together the light flame, that is the bullet the ray that departs from the silencer!

Halts suddenly, my arm, Yang Yanjia appears in the fist together carries on the back, „clang” a direct standard keeps off the attack of this bullet, at this time heard the bullet puts on silencer „scoffing” one, some people ambush me really here!

An arrow step, I swoop go forward, does not shoot the opportunity of second (spear|gun) to him, jumps, is in the airborne fist to change into fiery red, numerous rumbling!

„Whish!”

The hot band of light the cyclone is blowing down the surrounding flowers and plants, in a person hand of wear black jacket is taking the (spear|gun), on the face brings to visit me astonished, obviously has not thought of my speed quickly to this situation, but he is also well-trained, roared above nape of the neck to present a red scale of trim lowly, discarded the pistol, the nail extends sharp thorn claw thorns, nearly welcomed in the swing arm of roaring!

Really is breeds to think of the human, the A level dragon blood soldier!

In airborne, I turn the fist into the palm, supple vigor one group, „” opens out his arm suddenly, the left leg horizontal has pressed, in the intense collision sound, floods Yang Yanjin the left leg layer on layer to knock in his nape of the neck place, its pressure on the ground, the left fist takes advantage of opportunity directly strikes to pound to fall on his cheeks suddenly!

„Bang!”

The flame spatters in all directions, naked eye he spread on the scale to cheeks to wipe out many pieces by me obviously stiffly, under was wriggling the fearful muscle, my strength passed through the right fist suddenly, on the fist full was Yang Yanhuo the energy, opened the hand slowly, turned the fist into the blade, got down suddenly all at once, immediately the blood spattered in all directions, the head of this dragon blood soldier had rolled out, moreover surrounding flowers and plants also by Yang Yanhuo igniting, fierce has burnt.

Does not wait for me to stand up, the rear area hears the rumor suddenly, other?

Listens to the explaining away position, I stand up from failure to roll into the thick patch of grass suddenly, the body, from bottom to top one time explodes violently kicks!

„Bang!”

Center future front, but greets my as before is one piece by piece firm thick „dragon scale”, hasty under concentrates without enough time the Juyang flame vigor, only shakes numb the entire right leg, but he does not feel better, the whole person was kicked the nose oven to exit by my foot, the mouth spits the blood.

This has not calculated that the right is the consecutively two flames, my hurried airborne spin body avoidance, but on the arm transmits the burning ache, the bullet leans Yang Yanjia to pass, although has not wounded me, but lets me as but before ache.

Under the flame, two dragon blood soldiers launch the surprise attack from the right, but the left also presented one to wear the black clothed, in the hand is grasping a dragon blood soldier of handle shining Japan katana.

Bad, sets out 5 so-called dragon blood soldiers, is this must kill me?

The leaf came back from the native place, all renewals and activities resume the normal, this week's LOL live transmission activity change to start at 7 : 00 pm, channel 29216!

#1168: Forgives your way out!

Is the night, cold uncultivated land Dragon’s den also had the new movement, goes to the wild Dragon Clan territory to steal dragon egg, but the scale is quite big, Frost decided that leads 5000 + people to go to the wild Dragon Clan territory together, includes 100 Dragon Rider gentlemen . Moreover, I and Lin Wan Er, the Dong Cheng Yue three people also together accepted this Tier Main Quest.

In fact we that big scale is not steals dragon egg to be so simple, is snatches dragon egg simply.

Before placing, silver spear is known as „holding up of big dragon” the first dragon what kind power and prestige, we to steal dragon egg almost can make contact with the poor life, but now completely was different, along with Frost, child, Aodiliya cultivate for unceasing promotion, even if meets the silver spear also to strike to massacre him lossless, this also directly causes the silver spear to stealing dragon egg this matter almost turns a blind eye, has not definitely been able to make anything again.

, Also survival Dragon Clan immediately must split up gradually now is two, one is by silver spear Military Control wild Dragon Clan, another is the light that reason Shu leads is Dragon Clan, the Dragon Clan battle efficiency of wild Dragon Clan territory mainly came from in own blood relationship, but the cold uncultivated land Dragon’s den Dragon Clan strength came from the fusion with Dragon Rider gentleman bloodlines, the explosive force is stronger, the technicality is higher.

After the dark blue billows eradicate the seal regains consciousness, as if in the strength restoration rise, has still been dormant in the well of god demon does not have the sound, this is also we vigorously expands own good opportunity, in the silver spear not out of office Dragon Clan territory, like this we were also perhaps more convenient, child Shu has practiced into the god level Dragon Clan, the ordinary big dragon radically is not a match.

Sneak attacked Cooldown to decide at 11 : 00 pm, therefore our three are doomed tonight cannot rest on time, but for the [Zhan Long] Dragon Rider gentleman, endured!

Finished eating the dinner, sat cross-legged to sit in the bedside ground, according to the beforehand practice method, times pasted in within the body the strength, that heat flow flows in the meridians will actually not burn itself, but I can also feel that actually my body longs to this scalding hot strength, grew continually.

„Thump”

Outside hears the knock, Lin Wan Er said outside: „Crying foul, I wants to exit to stroll to meet the street with East city to come back to make the duty again, do you want to go together?”

This naturally must go, if makes Lin Tiannan and Dong Cheng Feng know that my to ignore treasure daughter alone window-shops, does not kill me to be strange.

Wears the clothes to go out rapidly, extreme gently beautifulness that two female both dress up, beyond young nous were many several points of smart-alecky aesthetic sense, I said: „Called Tang Qi?”

Dong Cheng Yue actually shakes the head: „Does not use, you can protect our two, why called Tang Qi, said again, many person many chopsticks, ate the snack time spent many.”

I deeply to be so: „Pours is also, a bit faster, quick 8 o'clock.”

„Um!”

The goal points to nearby pedestrian street, is actually too long has not gone out to stroll, two female both soon stuffily went bad.

Evening's pedestrian street, debauchery.

Has not walked far, in Dong Cheng Yue holds eats completely, the shrimp string and gefilte fish, roast the broccoli, eats does not forget to draw my sleeve, but Lin Wan Er is holding my hand, while looks at the two sides entertainment projects, anything shoots, fire, the ferrule circle to have, many sirs lead the child to play here.

„Feeds, looks at that side, has dozen of (spear|gun)s!”

Dong Cheng Yue have not scratched cleanly on draw I, said: „We played in the past!”

„Fires any (spear|gun)” I to be somewhat depressed.

She said immediately piteous: „In prize has the escape rabbit, I most liked that animation, but that escape rabbit balloon was good to be small, I definitely did not hit, Brother Xiao Yao helped me!”

Lin Wan Er throws smiles: „Good, you help her, East city seemingly truly ultra likes the escape rabbit, in her room is managing to various hands of escape rabbit with the puppet everywhere, this type, she has not collected.”

„Good” I am somewhat helpless.

The Lin Wan Er interest also came, followed me together.

This (spear|gun) hits the balloon to trade reward the stall is about 40 -year-old high and low uncle suspends, saw that two growth ultra good, the cheek ultra beauty comes, he eye soon fell immediately, said: „Ten money three (spear|gun)s, who can play?”

„Must play!” Lin Wan Er pulls out one 100 quickly, showed the local tyrant makings.

Uncle's happy accepting money, then took three (spear|gun)s to us, actually this is an air-gun, the bullet is the plastic, fires in the process the trajectory not to be unstable, moreover now on the pedestrian street has the wind, the wind speed is not low, therefore this trajectory is hard to judge, which does not point at really can project on, even if will be projects on may also use my plastic bullet strength unable to defeat the balloon insufficient, but many will suspend the person in this stall also on is makes money by this type, otherwise (spear|gun) compensated affirmative has in a big way sent.

Dong Cheng Yue scratches the clean hand, took the (spear|gun) „” to open there, what a pity the bullet randomly flew, did not hit, this girl inborn was not the expert marksman.

Lin Wan Er is actually very earnest, the posture that shows is also standard, she has studied the marksmanship with Lin Tiannan, this basic skill almost grasps with does not have what difference specialized, stall boss uncle who the one side surrounds noticed that Lin Wan Er the posture has shocked immediately, afterward the eye cannot move around others chests again.

What a pity, being hard control of plastic bullet makes Lin Wan Er have no alternative, the consecutively 3 (spear|gun)s failed.

The boss Ha Ha smiles in side: „Come on, girl.”

I somewhat was not feeling well, lift the hand to hold up the air-gun in my hand, Dong Cheng Yue visit me in side, said with a smile: „Brother Xiao Yao, it is said you are an expert marksman, making me have a look at the expert marksman fiercely!”

„!”

The first (spear|gun), failed.

The boss secretly titter, probably was saying that what expert marksman this is, Dong Cheng Yue comforts saying: „Has not related , to continue to refuel!”

The second (spear|gun), failed, the face of boss quickly smiled distorts.

The third (spear|gun), fails as before.

This time Dong Cheng Yue was speechless: „, Brother Xiao Yao you are the boasting king, radically is not the expert marksman.”

I laugh: „The conclusion, then again be not looking anxiously!”

Lin Wan Er also stopped the fire, have a relish visits me in side.

„Bang!”

The fourth (spear|gun), hit to explode a yellow balloon directly, obtained the prize is a young Wigny bear.

I have not stopped, fires two (spear|gun)s continuously again, the balloon explosive sound is unceasing, the first row of ballonet from left to right hits to explode continuously, afterward continues the filled plastics bullet, lifts the hand again, very standard firing position, „bang bang bang” consecutively three, hit the prize quite good balloon specially, moreover hitting from left to right, which refers to hitting, has not lost any (spear|gun) again.

Ahem, this small skill, does not permit the aiming of (spear|gun) every time actually, but my first round three (spear|gun)s fail to also let me completely confirmed that the aiming and true calibration disparity how many angles and distances, confirmed how many angle effect of wind speed on plastic bullet has, but after confirming these, I truly am the expert marksman of genuine goods at reasonable prices, by the marksmanship, Hangzhou approximately few that I am stronger than? Xiao Lie is one, other was difficult to say.

„That escape rabbit balloon of most top right-hand corner!” Dong Cheng Yue happy is holding my arm, said: „That blue balloon, Brother Xiao Yao helps me hit!”

I lift the hand, the balloon demolish accordingly, Dong Cheng Yue immediately on happy took the rag doll of escape rabbit.

The boss uncle's face quick was green, in an instant, his prize had is loaded into the plastic bag by Lin Wan Er and Dong Cheng Yue much, especially that only escape rabbit, works very fine, the goods at least over a hundred coins, therefore he blows very slightly that balloon of escape rabbit, the fist so is big, ahem, but cannot escape from my shooting with great precision.

„Was good, do not hit, one will take motionless.” I have put down the air-gun.

Lin Wan Er and Dong Cheng Yue happy nod.

The uncle also relaxed, my moral nature laughs in one's heart, keeps your way out, otherwise does not make your business owe to refuse stubbornly tonight to be possible! Probably uncle businessman also most feared that ran into my this professional, basically always lost.

Then, brings two female to shoot, crash-bang loses endlessly, does not know that has the technique content, but I was caught the mechanical games of toy defeating by metal finally, 50 coins throw, has not grasped including root hair, because also this matter was teased by two female for a long time.

Has played about 11 points time, finally gave up the return trip, when we arrived in the villa, Cooldown was also similar, got online, preparation tonight's sneak attack duty!

„Brushes!”

The characters appear in cold uncultivated land Dragon’s den, Lin Wan Er and Dong Cheng Yue also one after another get online, I summoned raspberry immediately, the Xiaolongnu howl, when I prepared to ride Long Bei, in this fellow transformed to throw child Shu to embrace for the human form rapidly went, harmed me to be in airborne, awkward hanging there, but started thousand frost wings, iced wing opening to stand in the wind, saves one point of face.

After having sufficed greasily, raspberry agree made me ride finally, but at this time, under the city had also heard an intermittent oppression of the people sound, 5000 Dragon’s den cavalries built up, Frost wielded the long sword, the order.

The dawn daybreak, the enormous and powerful crowd ran out of the snow expanse, bathes in the warm dawn, has washed off a coldness.

First the road section of process is the city of awe empire, what a pity, Luo Lin died here to turn into the ruins, continuous seeing had the cold uncultivated land Dragon’s den soldier to ship the city wall brick from here to the Dragon’s den direction, no wonder on the ice ridge mountain can the newly-built barriers, take the material of Luo Lin empire.

Across awe empire ruins time, around Frost somewhat absent-minded look, Luo Lin is her one massacres, but killed once good friend, made Frost cast the shadow eventually at heart.

I am riding raspberry low-altitude flying, at the same time to under was saying: „Past makes it pass.”

A Frost grateful nod: „Um!”

#1170: Ices the dragon surprise attack

„Child Shu, your this head ** dragon!”

Silver Golyan has the long sword, a face looks at child Shu angrily, the anger exclaims: „Have you forgotten once Long Shen the pledge? Will never form an alliance with humanity, did you forget? How enslaving Dragon Clan you forgot once humanity are, forgot Dragon Clan to bear the great suffering that? Now, you have humanity to come Long Yu, wants to destroy Long Yu thoroughly?”

Child Queen Shu lifts the cheek, distant looks at the silver spear, said lightly: „What qualifications does your this type plunder the lowly Saint dragon that others treat as wife to shout curses forcefully here? The silver spear, sacred Dragon Clan [lineage/vein] decline under your commanding day after day, haven't you seen all these? I only asked one, in wild Dragon Clan territory also some multi- discount sacred big dragons, over 50 heads? Perhaps did not have, do not forget, when Long Shen reigned, our sacred big dragon enough over 2000 heads!”

The silver spear lets somebody cool off or calm down smiles, said: „You were too exceptional, depends on your this red dragon flour ** can rally Dragon Clan?”

„Yes, I can, but that is after you died matter that can have, you do not need to inquire about.”

The child Shu corners of the mouth raise, lift the arm, said in a soft voice: „The Dragon Rider gentlemen, prepare to launch the attack!”

„Clang clang clang”

Rows of Dragon Rider gentlemen drew out Long Jian, before the sword blade edge have projected at least several meters sword air/Qi, after riding the big dragon, striking distance suddenly to increase, this was also the Dragon Rider gentleman most formidable place, fought with the Dragon Rider gentleman, not only need guard against the attack of mount dragon, must guard against the Dragon Rider gentleman own war technique attack, this was possibly more fearful.

On the silver spear face full is scowl, brandishes the long sword, roars lowly: „Dragon Clan, prepares to meet head-on! All sacred big dragon air attacks, the second-rate dragon and third-class dragon launch the attack from the ground, immediately kills to me, pursues from Dragon Clan this group of intruder, reduces the red dragon flour female prince Shu's head, making these traitors know that the Dragon Clan dignity is inviolable!”

A big dragon of leader sacred department appears in airborne, roared unceasingly, in ground, from the cave of surrounding mountain range unceasing the big dragon that drilled a leader, the big dragon quantity of fact Ueno Dragon Clan territory has gone far beyond our estimate, swept one sketchily, at least should have over a thousand big dragons!

„Roar roar!”

Airborne, a leader Thunder dragon, Black dragon, red dragon flour, the ice dragon and other sacred are the big dragon exudes the roaring sound, opens the great wing almost to spread the day to block out the sun, opens the big mouth, dragon rests fell.

„Shield!”

Frost is drinking loudly tenderly, the Dragon’s den armed soldiers take out the black to attach the demon shield to keep off in the front rapidly, has formed barrel, but that scalding hot dragon rest, once covers, these Dragon’s den armed soldiers certainly will be burnt, after all Longwei of big dragon is not false.

At this moment, Frost jumps to discontinue, a slippery step arrives at a shield front, the double pupil is facing directly the innumerable [say / way] dragon rest, suddenly drinks one lowly, the invisible bracing cold rapid surges for the center with her, a huge round arc defense cover appears in the surrounding, keeps off the dragon rest 11 standards, airborne flame chaotic dance, astonishing!

„Frost!”

Airborne hears the roaring sound, is the silver spear jumps to come impressively, both hands hold up the sword, is reappearing Black dragon this, on sword blade edge blazing fleeing flame and Lei Guang, is such certainly the world strikes, wants initially, the silver spear to be depended upon this to strike cleft in two cold uncultivated land Dragon’s den directly, now one's old tricks heavy, will be what kind of?

„Brushes!”

I have controlled raspberry to overrun, prepare to lead a cheer, after all the match is the silver spear, one of the ten big BOSS, Frost is also not necessarily able the whole body to draw back.

However, that at present has makes me feel that he thought many, Frost not only has not defended, instead the front surface went, cuts Hua Jian from the sky to tow a stars trace, radiant flame and incorruptible stars twinkles were unceasing, this came from the attack in day territory?

„Bang!”

Two strong strengths collide certainly in together, air currents surge to past in the surroundings, in Frost whole body gorgeously motionless being built on wind, cape under the air current surges the dance, reviewed the silver spear not to feel better, was shaken by a Frost sword backs up dozens meters, held on the arm of sword also to linger as before the stars ray, the complexion was pale.

„The strength of stars how?” Frost slightly smile.

The silver spear look is dignified, looks at Frost, said: „Did your you comprehend the strength of stars unexpectedly?”

„No, is not the comprehension, is my innermost soul had this strength.”

The Frost corners of the mouth raise, said: „Do not forget, superior Lord had the strength of control stars, this is almost an instinct.”

„”

The fresh breeze is swaying the cape of silver spear, he laughs fiercely, cleans blood that the corners of the mouth have seeped out, said: „Frost, you think that you have won? You think that the wild Dragon Clan territory is fighting single-handedly? You have made a mistake, ha”

Frost is indifferent, has not spoken.

Child Queen Shu the great anger, suddenly soars to the heavens to go, the right palm transforms is the dragon claw, roars: „Silver spear, have you forgotten once to my shaming? Suffers to death, the old lady dunned!”

„Humming sound”

In the sharp songs and calls, above the child Shu's right palm presented the strength of star territory, this is similar to the strength of strength of Frost stars, the star territory transforms for the roaring flame, the direct bang has approached the shoulder of silver spear.

„Frightens?”

The silver spear had a scare obviously, has not thought that the child Shu's strength large scale has also evolved, lifts the arm hurriedly, comes Georgian stop Queen Shu above the shoulder the sword blade edge horizontally the strikes.

The claw of red dragon flour falls swiftly and violently!

„Bang!”

The star territory changes into the shatter stars to surge, the silver spear has king level Hybrid Demon of strength of demon god after all, after own strength the dark blue billows directed, is progressed by leaps and bounds, but could not block child Shu as before the struck, bites the tooth, the space between teeth is spattering in all directions a blood as before, his arm was shivering fiercely, was struck the later right arm by Frost under the winding of strength of stars, where can stand up to child Shu struck fully?

„Clang!”

Child Shu same has drawn out waist saber, a Jianfeng spin is one time sweeps away!

The silver spear can only the hasty standard keep off, was actually shaken flies to draw back with the sword.

Child Shu treadons void, chases down rapidly, initially, the child Shu's body under the stupor received the infringement of silver spear, thinks that this regarding her was in the life the biggest shame, the silver spear does not die, this will linger at the nightmare of child enjoyable head never will dissipate.

„Bang bang bang”

Airborne, red flame and black flame spatter in all directions to explode unceasingly, the fight scenes of two big BOSS level Saint dragons are extremely magnificent, the entire wild Dragon Clan territory is almost shivering.

We have not helped in the fighting, Frost looks up the airborne tactical situation, I and Lin Wan Er, Dong Cheng Yue respectively resist one sacredly are the attacks of big dragon, coordinating the Dragon’s den armed soldier to hunt them!

The butterfly sword ray rises sharply, golden brilliance shoots up to the sky, the homemade skill rides the wind dividing that cuts to occupy a commanding position to cut above a head of fire dragon, carries over injury digit at the same time, this fire dragon also whins to crash, several Dragon’s den armed soldiers take out in abundance belay, „brushes” each spot of belaying fire dragon!

„Roar roar”

The fire dragon falls to the ground rapidly, actually likely is a giant flame lizard generally roars to struggle, the whole body proliferates the roaring flame, quick rope burning out.

The blue radish was slightly astonished, said: „It is not good, the ordinary rope is invalid to the fire dragon, it can summon the flame to proliferate the whole body, must use the steel and iron rope, hurry up, with shackle!”

The Dragon’s den armed soldiers do not delay Cooldown, took out heavy wire ropes from behind the travel bag of warhorse rapidly, „humming sound” dancing in the air is projecting, in an instant this fire dragon bundling a solidity, but it is whinning to struggle as before, does the sacred Dragon Clan dignity allow to encroach?

At this time, Seurre flew, looks that this fire dragon could not bear contemptuously smiles, suddenly jumped to fall, under the airborne longleg lifted presses, „bang” layer on layer a foot fell behind the head eye of fire dragon some positions, instantaneously this fire dragon knocking down, the strength of elf queen was really not a lid.

„”

Under not far away, two Dragon’s den armed soldiers emitted in roaring flame of red dragon flour turned into the ashes, before dying the cry to be pitiful, the blue radish and in Sirma overtook, this red dragon flour was also knocked in an instant down to fall to the ground to bind.

One after another, a leader sacred is the big dragon is knocked down in the place, but behind our bodies, a leader wind dragon, the green dragon and other low status Dragon Clan completely resists by the Dragon’s den armed soldier and Dragon Rider gentleman outside, but has the damage respectively, the Dragon’s den armed soldier after all is also only humanity, again well-trained impossible 1 V 1 selects the big dragon only, one group of people sphere one to have the stratagem which ensures success, but well in having Dragon Rider gentleman circles in airborne by the dragon rest reenforcement, otherwise was really difficult saying that who won who defeated.

„Bang!”

The airborne energy disintegration spatters in all directions, child Shu once again attacked fiercely with the offensive of silver spear has made into the evenly matched scene, the silver spear after a dozen minutes of restoration, finally started to be evenly matched with child Shu, but with falling from the sky of surrounding leader big dragon, the complexion of silver spear was also uglier, as if he also knows that this wild Dragon Clan territory soon was hit by the total destruction.

„What are you waiting for?” A child Shu face contemptuous happy expression, the left hand transformed Long Zhaozhong to beat severely in the shoulder of silver spear, immediately the blood spattered in all directions, one black Long Lin exited in the airborne flying shuttle.

The silver spear is Black dragon, the human under shape has Long Lin to protect oneself in fact, under the personal appearance draws back continually, the silver spear roars, said: „Child Shu, this is you courts death!”

Saying, the entire arm of silver spear was transforming the mail-armor and helmet to crack, the head also started becomes fierce, from was also the good-looking face becomes just likes black ink liao, the body also rapidly rose suddenly, the clothing was all torn into shreds by the rising crack, with „roar roar” Long recited, a giant Black dragon appeared in our front.

Child Shu sneers, is one roars, starts [Dragon Transformation]!

The next quarter, red dragon flour and a Black dragon in airborne worry mutually, Long Xi emits everywhere is, the entire sky as if changed colors.

„Guesses that child Shu Duochang Cooldown can kill the silver spear?” I said with a smile.

Lin Wan Er eats to smile: „Not over 5 minutes!”

„No, at least takes ten minutes!” Dong Cheng Yue assured [say / way].

„Look.” I said.

However at this moment, in the rear mountain range transmits Long Xiao suddenly, airborne has hiked up the snowflake, „”, a sturdy incorruptible big dragon arm holds in the mountain range peak, is a great mahatma dragon drops from the clouds, both feet step on treads the summit, an ejection overran, opens the huge mouth to above the child Shu's back.

My goodness, was one sacred is ices Long Jiaru to fight!